[
    {
        "question":"Electronics and technology company Siemens is headquartered in which country?",
        "answer":"Germany"
    },
    {
        "question":"In what year was the first 'Angry Birds' game released?",
        "answer":"2009"
    },
    {
        "question":"Amstrad was owned by which of these tycoons?",
        "answer":"Sir Alan Sugar"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which company makes the Bravia TVs?",
        "answer":"Sony"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which company made the VIC-20 home computer?",
        "answer":"Commodore"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the name for the small device which powers electric items when turned?",
        "answer":"Dynamo"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which company makes the DS handheld console?",
        "answer":"Nintendo"
    },
    {
        "question":"How many operational buttons did the original Game Boy have?",
        "answer":4
    },
    {
        "question":"Electrical charge is caused by the movement of what?",
        "answer":"Electrons"
    },
    {
        "question":"Philips and Sony introduced which product at the 1981 consumer electronics show?",
        "answer":"CD Player"
    },
    {
        "question":"A room designed to have minimal levels of static electricity, dirt, dust particles has which name?",
        "answer":"Clean Room"

    },
    {
        "question":"Broxodent was the first example of which electric product?",
        "answer":"Toothbrush"
    }
]